Hi, George!
Glad you're back, Loads of people have phoned you.
Really?
— I felt just like your secretary!
Sorry!
I went into the library this afternoon to have a look at a newspaper
and I came across something really interesting.
What?
A book?
— No, a brochure from a summer festival - mainly Spanish music.
Look, I've got it here.
Spanish music?
I really love the guitar.
Let's have a look.
So what's this group 'Guitarrini'?
They're really good.
They had a video with all the highlights of the festival at a stand
in the lobby to the library,
so I heard them.
They play fantastic instruments - drums and flutes and old kinds of guitars.
I've never heard anything like it before.
— Sounds great.
Okay.
Shall we go then?
Spoil ourselves?
— Yes, let's.
The only problem is there aren't any cheap seats.., it's all one price.
Well, in that case we could sit right at the front - we'd have
a really good view.
Yeah.
though I think that if you sit at the back you can actually hear
the whole thing better.
Yes.
Anyway we can decide when we get there.
So will you fill in the form or shall I?
I'll do it.
Name:
Georcle O'Neill.
Address:
48 North Avenue, Westsea.
Do you remember our new postcode?
Still can't remember it.
Just a minute - I've got it written down here.
WS6 2YH.
Do you need the phone too?
Please.
I'm really bad at numbers.
01674 553242.
So, let's book two tickets for Guitarrini.
Okay.
If you're sure ￡7.50 each is all right.
How do you feel about the singer?
I haven't quite decided.
But I've noticed something on the booking form that might just persuade me!
What's that then?
— Free refreshments!
— Really?
Yes, look here.
Sunday 17th of June.
Singer, ticket ￡6.00 includes drinks in the garden.
Sounds like a bargain to me!
Yes, let's book two tickets for that.
So, what else?
I'm feeling quite keen now!
How about the pianist on the 22nd of June?
Anna Ventura?
I've just remembered that's my evening class night.
That's okay.
I'll just have to go on my own - but we can go to the Spanish dance
and guitar concert together, can't we?
Yes - I'm sure Tom and Kieran would enjoy that too.
Good heavens - ￡10.50 a ticket!
I can see we're going to have to go without food for the rest
of the week - we'll need to book four!
Wish we were students - look!
Children, Students and Senior Citizens get a 50% discount on everything.
If only!